and
Another thing that I think many anyway
A little affected
It is a feeling that one wants to impress
There is a word for it in Swedish and it is
vanity
and vanity is the will to
be good and good
and impress others
simply appear as a very
good and good person
and that ... I can for example
feel it when I speak English
I understand that my English is not perfect
But somewhere in the back of my head so I would
want to be able to shine as one says
impress, have a perfect pronunciation
able to express me exactly
As I want because it feels pretty close
but
If I try to speak French
so it is more important that it is 100 %
clearly what one is talking about
and also most people want
Write correctly
one does not want to neglect too much when writing
so there is almost a little vanity there
Although the other would understand
so we want to write with the right
grammar, most of us
But it is also because there is a greater chance of it being
misunderstanding while writing